You're Su Muchen's sister?
Do you know why I asked you here?
I first met Zhou Jian
at a sword hall in France.
And this place
is a replica of
that sword hall.
You told Li Xiaorou
about Mumu?
How do you know?
My sister told me.
As for Li Xiaorou,
she knew from the beginning.
She even
told my sister about it.
Your hatred
is not just about Zhou Jian's betrayal.
What exactly is your purpose?
Lu Qianqian and Lu Xu are not siblings?
Yes.
After Mr. Lu passed away,
to get the 30% of the shares
left by Grandpa Lu to Lu Qianqian,
Annie adopted her from the orphanage.
Then, with her own efforts,
she took over the entire Lu family's business
and took over the early Golden Silk Group.
Without Grandpa Lu
to stop her from exploiting raw material suppliers,
she
used a price war to gain a head start,
and grew into the current Golden Silk Group.
Low cost, high profit.
What's wrong, Muchen?
Xiaorou,
can you help me get the information
of the suppliers back then?
What are you going to do?
I think
there are some things
I need to look into more deeply.
Isn't what you've found enough?
Muchen,
stop here.
Annie is not someone you can mess with.
If you keep going like this,
you'll get stuck in the mud.
I'm already stuck in the mud.
Help me.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you anymore.
You have to learn to face reality.
What else did Su Muchen find out?
You don't need to worry about it.
But you came to me today,
which means you're ready to break away from the Lu family.
Isn't that right?
You're very smart.
Soon,
the Lu family and I
will have no connection at all.
You're in such a hurry to see me.
Are you trying to confirm if I'm your target?
Now I know the answer.
I can transfer the 10% of shares to you.
But you must ensure
that Annie has no chance
to take Mumu from me.
You believe I can win?
At least now,
only you dare to compete with her.
I just want Mumu.
That's enough.
Okay.
I promise you.
Qianqian went to Singapore to find Dean Li.
She might
have known that you're not her biological mother.
And,
she has given away her shares.
4% of them
were bought by Zhuang Wan.
The remaining 11%
were transferred to Jiang Li
through a third party.
Mumu is not Zhou Jian's child,
but Lu Xu's.
She might know it.
What about Jiang Li?
Her name is Su Muli.
She is the sister of Su Muchen, Zhou Jian's ex-wife.
Su Muli.
The elder sister died in the fire.
The younger sister came to avenge her.
I thought she was just a scavenging dog.
I didn't expect
it was a demon.
How much does Jiang Li know
about what Su Muchen found out back then?
I'm not sure about that.
Better be safe than sorry.
If Jiang Li knows something she shouldn't,
Wu,
you know what to do.
Jenny, I know you're home.
I'd like to talk to you.
What do you want?
Just say it here.
Discuss my attempted murder at the door?
Are you sure?
Don't be so nervous.
I didn't call the police.
Are you that kind?
Of course not.
I have a condition.
What condition?
Are you just going to stand there and talk to me?
I can pretend nothing happened,
and you can keep being a fashion designer.
But I want the raw material test report
of the golden thread clothes your father hid.
I don't know anything.
All he left me after he died
was debt and a bottle of antidepressants.
What are you doing?
Don't come over.
[Parents working away from home.]
[Lived with grandmother since childhood.]
[Dreamed of becoming a fashion designer.]
[But was mocked and isolated by classmates.]
[Self-taught in fashion design.]
[Failed three art exams due to excessive nervousness.]
[Kneeled before design institutes seeking mentorship but was rejected.]
[Got into Golden Thread because her father]
[was an original employee.]
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I regretted
pushing you into the river.
I just want to design clothes
that make all girls look like fairy princesses.
I really want to design Dark Fairy Tale.
Jenny, do you know where the report is?
You know everything that happened back then, don't you?
I don't know.
You didn't go to Annie
but went to Lu Xu for cooperation after getting my materials.
because you were afraid of her,
weren't you?
Right?
I don't know.
Don't push me anymore.
I don't know anything.
Who are you?
What do you want these files for?
Some secrets shouldn't be hidden.
The victims deserve justice.
Your parents gave you a chance with their lives,
not to associate with the devil.
A designer's hands should hold brushes and needles,
not weapons.
I'll give you time to think it over.
Jiang Li, are you crazy?
Why did you go to Jenny alone?
He almost killed you.
I'm not dead, am I?
Since you accepted my help,
you shouldn't hide anything from me.
I just want to avenge my sister.
You know that.
Jiang Li.
The fire in the chemical fiber factory 20 years ago
was not an accident.
You didn't tell me anything.
Shen Jingmo.
Before we met at the convenience store,
I don't remember when and where I met you.
Why are you always following me like a shadow?
Because you once warmed countless people like the sun.
[I was one of them.]
[I know there are many people like me in the world.]
[But I think]
[I'm the luckiest one.]
[Because I]
[can meet you again.]
This is my sister's diary.
She wanted to prove the child wasn't Zhou Jian's through genetic testing,
but she accidentally discovered the truth about my parents' death.
The predecessor of Golden Thread, Xingyue Group,
rotten meat under the bright appearance.
[They used synthetic fibers to pass off as silk.]
Su Mingyuan,
are you out of your mind?
This could land you in prison!
Keep your voice down!
After Mr. Lu's death,
President An took over Xingyue.
She gave us two options:
either get out of Xingyue's supply chain,
or accept their low prices.
It's hard to find a client
with such a large demand as Xingyue Group.
If we're kicked out of their supply chain,
we'll have to lay off half of our staff.
These are employees who have been with me for over a decade.
They have families to support,
with elders to care for
and children to raise.
I can't bear to lay off anyone.
But now we're getting customer complaints
of allergic reactions and skin ulcers.
We're risking people's health
to earn a living for our factory.
How could you come up
with such a conscienceless solution?
It's all Assistant Wu's fault.
He told me to do it.
He said as long as we help Xingyue win this price war,
the acquisition price will return to what it was before.
He also said
that Xingyue would take responsibility for any issues.
I heard
[reporters are already investigating this.]
If it's exposed,
the factory will be done for.
Mingyuan,
where are you going so late?
I have something to do.
I'll be back soon.
[Later, I found out that night,]
[Dad went out to meet Assistant Wu.]
What do you mean by this?
The money in here
for rebuilding the new factory.
Destroy all the synthetic materials
before it's exposed.
Destroy?
How do I destroy them?
Water?
Fire?
Whatever.
Just make sure they're destroyed thoroughly.
So your father caused a short circuit
to create an accident on purpose.
But your mother didn't know that,
so she went in to put out the fire.
As a result, your father saved your mother.
Cause and effect.
My father's price for dealing with the devil.
But the real culprit
is those who manipulate the lives of others behind the scenes.
So,
what are you going to do next?
Jenny is unwilling to show the clothing test report from that year
because she is afraid of Annie.
to pry off the diamonds under Annie's crown
at the next shareholders' meeting.
Zhuang Wan's shares are crucial.
Okay.
There are so many women in the world,
but you fell in love with the one you shouldn't.
You made Lu Qianqian pregnant.
I concealed everything for your own good.
Why don't you listen to me?
Why did you open that Pandora's box?
At this time,
shouldn't you be taking Mumu to school?
This morning, the Madam took the Young Master to the airport.
She said she was going to Switzerland to see the snow.
Switzerland?
Where's Zhou Jian?
Isn't he with them?
The Master went to Milan for procurement a few days ago.
He won't be back until next week.
Got it.
You can go.
OK.
Wu,
freeze Lu Qianqian's card.
Find out where she took Mumu as soon as possible.
Why are you crying?
Is it because I'm not good?
You are the best baby in the world.
I'll take you to the Alps for snow.
and to Nara to feed the deer.
From now on,
no old house,
no etiquette class,
only Mumu and Mom's adventure.
What about Dad?
Grandma said she would take me on a big cruise at Christmas.
They are all too busy
to spend time with Mumu.
So from now on,
Mom is the only family Mumu has in the world.